The Overwatch heroes have a difficulty rating between one and three,
except for Bastion who has a difficulty rating of seven.
So, to counter that literally every pro player picked Bastion, Blizzard added a new sniper hero.
But do not worry, fellow robots.
Today I'm going to show you how to defeat Ana on three random maps.
Playing Skirmish, obviously.
Because I'm not here to show you how to park a car.
I'm here to teach you how to hunt grandma.
Honestly, the best thing about Overwatch;
punching these things while waiting.
It's just so much fun!
Oh great, it's the village!
Then I can show you how to make this jump without Ultimate.
I actually have no idea how to do this, why did I even promise that?
Anyway, as you can see, Ana is very easy to take out.
It's also very entertaining.
I could do this forever.
Next map.
That's... actually pretty neat.
I didn't know the same map could show up twice.
But for some reason, Ana is gone.
W-whatever, I'll just wait out the time.
That's... weird.
Is this a glitch?
Hmm, so the escape button is not working, then I tried to turn off the computer, but I can't leave my chair.
So, considering it's affecting reality, it's probably not a bug.
Unless Blizzard really, really messed up the last patch.
24 hours in this place!
What's going on here?
Think, what could be the simplest explaination?
It needs to be something that is easy to do, but can also bend the space-time continuum.
Of course...
I'm getting hacked!
But who hates -me-?
I guess the entire Overwatch community because I always pick Bastion...
No.
This has to be my software engineer friend.
Because I stole his copy of GTA IV.
I also tried to kill his dog...
...but that was justified.
My chocolate bar tasted bad and there was no place to throw it away.
Wait, I can't get hacked!
I have an iMac!
♫ I come from the land down under... ♫
...oh!
Just remembered, I said "I could do this forever".
Maybe a magical object is responsible for this.
I was standing right here when I said it.
The only object near me is... uh...
D-do these half painted planks grant wishes?
One week has passed.
Uh... should have died from dehydration.
But I haven't.
So, that's nice.
This place, though.
Getting... kinda boring.
How did Murray get out of this?
That's right, he started doing good deeds.
Oh.
Right.
I guess that rules out goat sacrifice.
Oh god, it's so obvious.
I promised to show everyone how to do that jump.
I am stuck here because of karma.
Okay, I am going to do it.
Even if it takes me an entire year.
[music plays]
[Kilian makes a bird noise]
[bird noise echoes]
[Kilian makes another noise]
[other noise echoes]
♫ Punch a vase, and then punch another vase. ♫
♫ Punch a vase, and by then it's... ♫
...oh god, I'm so tired of this vase-infested map.
♫ [exhausted] I got you babe, duh-duh, duh-duh, duh-duh. ♫
Huh...
It's time.
That would be amazing.
And also impossible.
I don't know who did this to me.
But, uh, what can you do?
It might be someone doing it just for fun.
Just...
Fun...
"It's just so much fun!"
Oh...
[sighs]
I'm sorry I punched you in the face 8760048 times.
[distorted] Thy curse has been lifted.
But please stop playing Bastion.
No!
I got some time left...
This could be my last chance to redeem myself.
No...